financial-inv.com 2013-09-03

# financial-inv.com

### Privacy Policy

Assurance that the private details that a client provides to a company while signing up with them will be kept classified is stated by privacy policy. We, at financial-inv.com, ensure you non-disclosure of the enlisted personal data to any third party: 

  * Client’s full name
  * Client’s full address and ZIP code
  * Client’s telephone number, mobile number and fax
  * Information related to payments
  * Information regarding the activities of the client in the service
  * Information related to the Internet Provider of the client, browser or speed of internet connection.

However, this personal information may be used by us for internal purposes alone. This is necessary to perform certain operation and in order to improve our quality of service that makes use of your private information. These operations and services include: administration of the website, sending invoices and statements to you, collection of payment, sending newsletters, business related information and notification, to solve your problems, complaints and enquiries and to enhance our clients’ browsing experience by customizing the website. It may also be stored, processed and transmitted to any country in which we function. If you have opened your account with us and have now changed your address, contact number or email id, or if any correction is to be made, please inform us about these changes so that we can keep our database updated.

Our company assures you that none of these details will ever be revealed to anyone except under the following circumstances:

  * If we have received a court order requesting the release of information in regard to any current or potential legal proceeding.
  * To establish, execute and preserve our legal rights and authority.

We give you full authority to order us to provide you with the information we hold about you. However, you can make use of this provision only by verifying your identity by providing any legal document, such as Voter’s Card or Social Security Number. For us, ensuring optimum privacy for our customers is very important. We make every effort and take each technological and organizational measure to prevent loss, misuse or alteration of our client’s personal details. We have firewall and password protected servers to store these vital information. However, we take no responsibility for the privacy provided by third party websites who have their links on our website.

If we ever make any amendment or changes in our privacy policy, a notification is sent to all the clients’ via email. Investors are also requested to let us know if they have any objection to any amendment or change we have made. We value your advice. So if you have any suggestions to make related to our privacy policy and the way we handle your private information, you can contact our team.
